Whatever you do don't ever play my game
Too many years being the king of pain
You gotta lose it all if you wanna take control
Sell yourself to save your soul
Rescue me
From the demons in my mind
From the lovers in my life
Rescue Me
From the demons in my mind
Rescue me
Whatever you do don't ever lose your faith
The devil's quick to love lust and fame
Better to say yes than never know
Ooh
Sell yourself to save your soul
Rescue me
From the demons in my mind
From the lovers in my life
Rescue me
From the demons in my mind
Sell yourself to save your soul
(You gotta)
Rescue me
From the demons in mind
From the lovers in my life
Rescue me
From the demons in my mind