♪♪♪
♪ LIVING IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ 'NEATH HEAVENS TORN ASUNDER ♪
♪ YOU CALL ON ME ♪
♪ TO SOLVE A CROOKED RHYME ♪
♪ AS I'M CLOSING IN ♪
♪ IMPOSING ON YOUR SLUMBER ♪
♪ YOU CALL ON ME ♪
♪ AS BELLS BEGINS TO CHIME ♪
♪ ARE YOU ON THE SQUARE? ♪
♪ ARE YOU ON THE LEVEL? ♪
♪ ARE YOU READY TO SWEAR
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ BEFORE THE DEVIL? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE ON THE SQUARE? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE ON THE LEVEL? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE READY TO STAND
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ HIDING FROM THE LIGHT ♪
♪ SACRIFICING NOTHING ♪
♪ STILL YOU YOU CALL ON ME ♪
♪ FOR ENTRANCE TO THE SHRINE ♪
♪ HAMMERING THE NAILS ♪
♪ INTO A SACRED COFFIN ♪
♪ YOU CALL ON ME ♪
♪ FOR POWERS CLANDESTINE ♪
♪ ARE YOU ON THE SQUARE? ♪
♪ ARE YOU ON THE LEVEL? ♪
♪ ARE YOU READY TO SWEAR
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ BEFORE THE DEVIL? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE ON THE SQUARE? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE ON THE LEVEL? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE READY TO STAND
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪♪♪
♪ ARE YOU ON THE SQUARE? ♪
♪ ARE YOU ON THE LEVEL? ♪
♪ ARE YOU READY TO SWEAR
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ BEFORE THE DEVIL? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE ON THE SQUARE? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE ON THE LEVEL? ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE READY TO STAND
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ RIGHT HERE, RIGHT ♪
♪ NOW ♪