♪ DON'T NEED PERMISSION ♪
♪ MADE MY DECISION ♪
♪ TO TEST MY LIMITS ♪
♪ CUZ IT'S MY BUSINESS ♪
♪ GOD AS MY WITNESS ♪
♪ START WHAT I FINISHED ♪
♪ DON'T NEED NO HOLD UP ♪
♪ TAKING CONTROL OF ♪
♪ THIS KINDA MOMENT ♪
♪ I'M LOCKED AND LOADED ♪
♪ COMPLETELY FOCUSED ♪
♪ MY MIND IS OPEN ♪
♪ ALL THAT YOU GOT ♪
♪ SKIN TO SKIN ♪
♪ OH MY GOD ♪
♪ DON'T CHYA STOP, BOY ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU ♪
♪ MAKES ME FEEL LIKE ♪
♪ A DANGEROUS WOMAN ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT,
SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU ♪
♪ MAKES ME WANNA DO ♪
♪ THINGS THAT I SHOULDN'T ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT, SOMETHING
'BOUT, SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ NOTHING TO PROVE AND ♪
♪ I'M BULLETPROOF AND ♪
♪ KNOW WHAT I'M DOING ♪
♪ THE WAY WE'RE MOVING ♪
♪ LIKE INTRODUCING ♪
♪ US TO A NEW THING ♪
♪ I WANNA SAVOR ♪
♪ SAVE IT FOR LATER ♪
♪ THE TASTE, THE FLAVOR ♪
♪ CUZ I'M A TAKER,
CUZ I'M A GIVER ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY NATURE ♪
♪ I LIVE FOR DANGER ♪
♪ ALL THAT YOU GOT ♪
♪ SKIN TO SKIN ♪
♪ OH MY GOD ♪
♪ DON'T CHYA STOP, BOY ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU ♪
♪ MAKES ME FEEL LIKE ♪
♪ A DANGEROUS WOMAN ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT,
SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU ♪
♪ MAKES ME WANNA DO ♪
♪ THINGS THAT I SHOULDN'T ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT,
SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ ALL GIRLS
WANNA BE LIKE THAT ♪
♪ BAD GIRLS
UNDERNEATH LIKE THAT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW HOW
I'M FEELING INSIDE ♪
♪ ALL GIRLS
WANNA BE LIKE THAT ♪
♪ BAD GIRLS
UNDERNEATH LIKE THAT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW HOW
I'M FEELING INSIDE ♪
♪♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU ♪
♪ FEEL LIKE A
DANGEROUS WOMAN ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT,
SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU ♪
♪ WANNA DO THINGS
THAT I SHOULDN'T ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT,
SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ ALL GIRLS
WANNA BE LIKE THAT ♪
♪ BAD GIRLS
UNDERNEATH LIKE THAT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW HOW I'M FEELING ♪
♪ SAY YOU KNOW HOW
I'M FEELING INSIDE ♪
♪ NEATH LIKE THAT ♪
♪ BAD GIRLS
UNDERNEATH LIKE THAT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW HOW
I'M FEELING INSIDE ♪
♪ YA THERE'S
SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU BOY ♪
♪ YA THERE'S SOMETHING
'BOUT YOU BOY ♪
♪ YA THERE'S
SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU BOY ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT,
SOMETHING 'BOUT ♪
♪ YA THERE'S
SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU VOCODER ♪
SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU BOY ♪
♪ YA THERE'S SOMETHING
'BOUT YOU BOY ♪
♪ SOMETHING 'BOUT YOU ♪