♪♪
♪ WHEN WE WERE YOUNG THE
FUTURE WAS SO BRIGHT ♪
♪ THE OLD NEIGHBORHOOD
WAS SO ALIVE ♪
♪ AND EVERY KID ON THE
WHOLE DAMN STREET ♪
♪ WAS GONNA MAKE IT BIG
AND NOT BE BEAT ♪
♪ NOW THE NEIGHBORHOOD'S
CRACKED AND TORN ♪
♪ THE KIDS ARE GROWN UP BUT
THEIR LIVES ARE WORN ♪
♪ HOW CAN ONE LITTLE STREET ♪
♪ SWALLOW SO MANY LIVES ♪
♪ CHANCES THROWN ♪
♪ NOTHING'S FREE ♪
♪ LONGING FOR WHAT USED TO BE ♪
♪ STILL IT'S HARD ♪
♪ HARD TO SEE ♪
♪ FRAGILE LIVES,
SHATTERED DREAMS ♪
♪♪
♪ JAMIE HAD A CHANCE,
WELL SHE REALLY DID ♪
♪ INSTEAD SHE DROPPED OUT AND
HAD A COUPLE OF KIDS ♪
♪ MARK STILL LIVES AT HOME
CAUSE HE'S GOT NO JOB ♪
♪ HE JUST PLAYS GUITAR AND
SMOKES A LOT OF POT ♪
♪ JAY COMMITTED SUICIDE ♪
♪ BRANDON OD'D AND DIED ♪
♪ WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON ♪
♪ THE CRUELEST DREAM, REALITY ♪
♪ CHANCES THROWN ♪
♪ NOTHING'S FREE ♪
♪ LONGING FOR WHAT USED TO BE ♪
♪ STILL IT'S HARD ♪
♪ HARD TO SEE ♪
♪ FRAGILE LIVES,
SHATTERED DREAMS ♪
♪♪
♪ CHANCES THROWN ♪
♪ NOTHING'S FREE ♪
♪ LONGING FOR WHAT USED TO BE ♪
♪ STILL IT'S HARD ♪
♪ HARD TO SEE ♪
♪ FRAGILE LIVES,
SHATTERED DREAMS ♪