Sharpening blades in dreams of terror
Your fury is what you are
Increasing lust of a living hate
Again an again in a physical pain
Her profanation's ready
*The sacrifice is on its way*
The resonating screams arise
Until she dies, in her own blood
She's drowning down
*You* Can't escape from your own nature
Forever's who you are!
Drain all her will to resist whitout any respect
The scars you've done will be impressed like a mark on her back
A desecration's coming
*The eyes you've never seen are closed*
The sound of her breath drifts away
Forever gone
Burn!
Forever burn
-All her dreams-
-She feels lost and facing the insanity-
*We're lost in this pain*
-Her whisper is fading away-
-Destiny won't forgive-
*Won't* forgive the one who lead to the unmerciful fate!
Pray all your gods to be saved
You can not liberate
Your wicked soul from the dread of a tragical fate
«Our inquisition is coming to punish your life»
The sound of her scream makes you mad
The sin is done
Stalking preys with frantic sadism
Your evil's satisfied
Incoming will to devastate
Again an again in a critical haze
The snow white skin is burning
*Impurity for all to see*
Her shattered body is on the ground
Until she dies, In her own blood
She's drowning down
*You* Can't escape from your own nature
Forever's who you are!
Forever burn
-All her dreams-
-She feels lost and facing the insanity-
*We're lost in this pain*
-Her whisper is fading away-
Destiny won't forgive
*Won't* forgive the one who lead to the unmerciful fate!
For this crime you'll be trapped in our cage
And again you'll be slave to the rage
We will impose the sentence of your death
For your demise
While you beg for a mercy denied
We'll be deaf and our purification will be blind
This violation will condamn to die