("Human")
♪ I did my best to notice ♪
♪ When the call came down the line ♪
♪ Up to the platform of surrender ♪
♪ I was broad but I was kind ♪
♪ And sometimes I get nervous ♪
♪ When I see an open door ♪
♪ Close your eyes ♪
♪ Clear your heart ♪
♪ Cut the cord ♪
♪ Are we human ♪
♪ Or are we dancer ♪
♪ My sign is vital ♪
♪ My hands are cold ♪
♪ And I'm on my knees ♪
♪ Looking for the answer ♪
♪ Are we human ♪
♪ Or are we dancer ♪
♪ Pay my respects to grace and virtue ♪
♪ Send my condolences to good ♪
♪ Give my regards to soul and romance ♪
♪ They always did the best they could ♪
♪ And so long to devotion ♪
♪ You taught me everything I know ♪
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
♪ Wish me well ♪
♪ You got to let me go ♪
♪ Are we human ♪
♪ Or are we dancer ♪
♪ My sign is vital ♪
♪ My hands are cold ♪
♪ And I'm on my knees ♪
♪ Looking for the answer ♪
♪ Are we human ♪
♪ Or are we dancer ♪
♪ Will your system be alright ♪
♪ When you dream of home tonight ♪
♪ There is no message we're receiving ♪
♪ Let me know is your
heart still beating ♪
♪ Are we human ♪
♪ Or are we dancer ♪
♪ My sign is vital ♪
♪ My hands are cold ♪
♪ And I'm on my knees ♪
♪ Looking for the answer ♪
♪ You got to let me know ♪
♪ Are we human ♪
♪ Or are we dancer ♪
♪ My sign is vital ♪
♪ My hands are cold ♪
♪ And I'm on my knees ♪
♪ Looking for the answer ♪
♪ Are we human ♪
♪ Or are we dancer ♪