FUCK REALLY?
WHAT THE FUCK?
YO MAN ARE WE GOING TO
THE STUDIO OR WHAT?
YEAH LETS GO HOLD ON
I KEEP GETTING FUCKING
ALERTS ON MY PHONE
ALERTS?
YA LIKE ARTICLES
AND SHIT
EMINEM COMPLETELY
PHONES IN HIS VERSE
FUCK THIS
WHAT WRONG WITH HIM?
HE GOTTA STOP LOOKING
AT THAT SHIT GOD DAMN
♪ YOU KNOW ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S BEEN TELLING ME
WHAT THEY THINK ABOUT ME ♪
♪ FOR THE LAST FEW MONTHS ♪
♪ MAYBE ITS TIME THAT
I THINK ABOUT THEM ♪
♪ GOTTA CONCENTRATE
AGAINST THE CLOCK ♪
♪ I RACE GOT NO TIME TO WASTE ♪
♪ I'M ALREADY LATE I GOT
A MARATHONER'S PACE ♪
♪ WENT FROM ADDICT TO A
WORKAHOLIC WORD TO DR. DRE ♪
♪ AND THAT FIRST
MARIJUANA TAPE ♪
♪ GUESS I GOT A CHRONIC CASE ♪
♪ AND I AIN'T JUST
BLOWIN' SMOKE ♪
♪ LESS IT'S IN
YOUR MAMA'S FACE ♪
♪ I KNOW THIS TIME PAUL
AND DRE THEY WON'T TELL
ME WHAT NOT TO SAY ♪
♪ AND THOUGH ME AND
MY PARTY DAYS ♪
♪ HAVE ALL PRETTY
MUCH PARTED WAYS ♪
♪ YOU SWEAR TO GOD I FORGOT I'M
THE GUY WHO MADE "NOT AFRAID" ♪
♪ ONE LAST FOR CHARLAMAGNE ♪
♪ IF MY RESPONSE IS LATE THAT'S
JUST HOW LONG IT TAKES ♪
♪ TO HIT MY FUCKIN'
RADAR I'M SO FAR AWAY ♪
♪ THESE RAPPERS ARE
LIKE HUNGER GAMES ♪
♪ ONE MINUTE THEY'RE
MOCKING JAY ♪
♪ NEXT MINUTE THEIR GET
THERE STYLE FROM MIGOS ♪
♪ OR THEY COPY DRAKE ♪
♪ MAYBE I JUST DON'T KNOW WHEN
TO TURN AROUND AND WALK AWAY ♪
♪ BUT ALL THE HATE I CALL IT
"WALK ON WATER-GATE" ♪
♪ I'VE HAD AS MUCH AS
I CAN TOLERATE ♪
♪ I'M SICK AND
TIRED OF WAITIN' ♪
♪ I'V LOST MY PATIENTS I CAN
TAKE ALL OF YOU MOTHERFUCKERS ♪
♪ ON AT ONCE YOU WANTED SHADY ♪
♪ YOU GOT HIM ♪
♪ DON'T FALL ON MY FACE ♪
♪ DON'T FALL ON MY FAITH, OH ♪
♪ DON'T FALL ON MY FATE ♪
♪ SOMEBODY TELL BUDDEN BEFORE I
SNAP HE BETTER FASTEN IT ♪
♪ OR HAVE HIS BODY BAG GET
ZIPPED THE CLOSEST THING ♪
♪ HE'S HAD TO HITS IS
SMACKIN' BITCHES ♪
♪ AND DON'T MAKE ME HAVE TO
GIVE IT BACK TO ACADEMICS ♪
♪ SAY THIS SHIT IS TRASH
AGAIN I'LL HAVE YOU TWISTED ♪
♪ LIKE YOU HAD IT WHEN YOU
THOUGHT YOU HAD ME SLIPPIN' ♪
♪ AT THE TELLY EVEN WHEN
I'M GETTING "BRAIN" ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER CATCH ME WITH A
THOT (THOUGHT) LACKING WITH IT ♪
♪ "HE AIN'T SPITTIN' LIKE
THIS ON HIS LAST SHIT" ♪
♪ HOE YOU BETTER GO
BACK AND LISTEN ♪
♪ YOU KNOW ME BETTER
THINKIN' I'LL SLOW ♪
♪ OR LET UP CALL IT
TRAP 'CAUSE IT'S A ♪
♪ TOTAL SET UP HOPIN' THAT YOU
RAPPERS FALL IN THAT DRE SAID ♪
♪ "HOLD YOUR HEAD"
UP KATHY GRIFFIN ♪
♪ STACKIN' AMMUNITION SLAP
THE CLIP IN COCK IT BACK ON ♪
♪ COMPETITION THIS IS
HOW I SHOT A-HEAD ♪
♪ GABBY GIFFORD ♪
♪ MY ATTACK IS VICIOUS JACK
THE RIPPER BACK IN BUSINESS ♪
♪ TYLER CREATE NOTHIN' I SEE
WHY YOU CALLED YOURSELF A ♪
♪ BITCH IT'S NOT JUST
'CAUSE YOU LACK ATTENTION ♪
♪ IT'S BECAUSE YOU
WORSHIP D-12'S BALLS
YOU'RE SACK RELIGIOUS ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE GONNA
CRITIQUE ME YOU BETTER AT
LEAST BE AS GOOD OR ♪
♪ BETTER GET "EARL THE
HOODED SWEATER" ♪
♪ WHATEVER HIS NAME IS TO
HELP YOU PUT TOGETHER ♪
♪ SOME WORDS MORE THAN JUST
TWO LETTERS THE FANS ♪
♪ WAITED FOR THIS MOMENT
LIKE THAT FEATURE WHEN ♪
♪ I STOLE THE SHOW SORRY
IF I TOOK FOREVER ♪
♪ DON'T FALL ON MY FACE ♪
♪ DON'T FALL ON MY FAITH, OH ♪
♪ DON'T FALL ON MY FATE ♪
♪ JUST REMEMBER I WAS
HERE BEFORE YOU ♪
♪ AND I'LL BE HERE AFTER YOU
MAKE YOUR RUN AND FOR YOU ♪
♪ DETRACTORS I'MA HAVE TO FUCK
PITCHFORK WITH A CORK SCREW ♪
♪ JUST WHAT THE
DOCTOR ORDERED ♪
♪ REVENGE IS THE BEST MEDICINE ♪
♪ INCREASE THE DOSE
FROM LEAST TO MOST ♪
♪ AND THEN TELL
THE GRAMMIES TO GO ♪
♪ AND FUCK THEMSELVES THEY SUCK
THE BLOOD FROM ALL THE BIGGEST ♪
♪ ARTISTS LIKE SOME LEECHES SO ♪
♪ THEY NOMINATE 'EM
GET 'EM THERE GET A
NAME TO MC THE SHOW ♪
♪ EVERY PARASITE NEEDS A HOST ♪
♪ THEN GIVE ALBUM OF THE
YEAR TO SOMEBODY THAT NO ♪
♪ ONES EVER EVEN HEARD OF
ALL I KNOW IS THAT I WROTE ♪
♪ EVERY SINGLE WORD OF
EVERYTHING I EVER MURDERED ♪
♪ TIME TO SEPARATE THE
SHEEP FROM GOATS ♪
♪ AND I GOT NO FAITH
IN YOUR WRITERS ♪
♪ I DON'T BELIEVE IN GHOSTS ♪
♪ BUT WHEN RAP NEEDED IT MOST I
WAS THAT WING AND A PRAYER ♪
♪ A BEACON OF HOPE (BEAK & A
HOPE) PUT A B-I-R-D IN THE AIR ♪
♪ SOMEWHERE SOME KID IS
BUMPIN' THIS WHILE HE LIP
SYNCHS IN THE MIRROR ♪
♪ THAT'S WHO I'M DOIN' IT
FOR THE REST I DON'T
REALLY EVEN CARE ♪
♪ BUT YOU WOULD THINK I'M
CARRYING A OXFORD
DICTIONARY IN MY POCKET ♪
♪ HOW I'M BURYING THESE ARTISTS
ON A SCALE OF "TURNT" ♪
♪ YOU'RE "MINUS" MINE SAYS
"VERY" YOURS SAYS "HARDLY" ♪
♪ AND WHAT'S SCARY IS
YOU PROBABLY CAN COMPARE
ME TO YOUR CAR ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M JUST BARELY
GETTING' STARTED ♪
♪ AND FAR AS LORD JAMAR YOU
BETTER LEAVE ME THE HELL ALONE ♪
♪ OR I'LL SHOW YOU AN
ELVIS CLONE WALK UP IN
THIS HOUSE YOU OWN ♪
♪ THRUST MY PELVIC BONE ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD TELEPHONE THEN
GO FETCH ME THE REMOTE ♪
♪ PUT MY FEET UP AND JUST
MAKE MYSELF AT HOME ♪
♪ I BELONG HERE CLOWN DON'T
TELL ME 'BOUT THE CULTURE ♪
♪ I INSPIRED THE HOPSIN'S
THE LOGIC'S THE COLES THE ♪
♪ SEAN THE K DOT'S THE
FIVE NINE'S AND OH ♪
♪ BROUGHT THE WORLD 50 CENT ♪
♪ YOU DID SQUAT PISS & MOAN
BUT I'M NOT GONNA FALL ♪
♪ BITCH YEAH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ SO YEAH ♪
♪ YOU CAN'T HEAR IT
COMING DOWN THE HALLWAY ♪
♪ FROM THE PARKING LOT ♪
♪ IT'S TO LOUD ♪
♪ HE'S FROM THE
CROWD ALL UP IN IT ♪
♪♪♪