Welcome to the nightmare
where villains wear the crowns
Fools rule a broken world
and fear grows all around
There's a bad king
A dreadful puppet on a string
He pretends to be a champion
of the common man
Wants more division
in his lost and riven land
He plays with real lives
in the darkest game of life
His greedy eyes
Looks insane, frozen smile like he's in pain
He doesn't count
The human cost but only money made or lost
King for a day
He kills the truth and looks away
Lives like the world would end today
King for a day
What do you hide, why do you lie?
Who made the rules for this game?
Who is paying your champagne?
All the mercy in the world
cannot save you anymore
King for a day
He knows how to justify
and how to feed the myths
How to glorify
the lies and hide the truth
He talks a lot but
his mouth is full of empty words
He has the right friends
making shady inside deals
Before the story ends
we will be out of tears
Fools give the answer
wise men don't even try
The time has come
To dethrone him but there's a new clone
stepping in
Just more scum
Another greedy, rotten puppet on a string
King for a day
He kills the truth and looks away
Lives like the world would end today
King for a day
What do you hide, why do you lie?
Who made the rules for this game?
Who is paying your champagne?
All the mercy in the world
cannot save you anymore
King for a day
I own the seas
I have the Earth on its knees
Give me another day
And I'll take your future away
Just vote for me - again
King for a day
he kills the truth and looks away
lives like the world would end today
King for a day
What do you hide, why do you lie?
Who made the rules for this game?
Who is paying your champagne?
All the mercy in the world
cannot save you anymore
King for a day