-Ohh,
Bright son of destiny-
-Bringer of light in this darkness-
-Beautiful prince-
-Now take my hand again-
-Forever tied by the thread of our fate-
-Now, we're together again-
Cold and desolate is the nature of my soul
Forever indifferent to the screams of shadows
Lying deep in the void
So give it up
Now face the score
In the heart of the chosen one
There's no deliverance!
«I have to face all this scorn»
«Staining my own land with useless tears»
«Look in the eyes of the one»
«Feeding himself with my deepest fears»
-Ohh,
I'll touch your heart again-
-Waken the cold lonely dreamer-
-I, will illuminate your soul-
-Wounded by emptiness-
-Please take me far from this land of pain-
-Now, on the waves of the sea-
Cold and desolate is the nature of my soul
Forever indifferent to the screams of shadows
Lying deep in the void
So give it up
Now face the score
In the heart of the chosen one
There's no deliverance!
I had to face all this scorn
Staining my own land with useless tears
Look,
Now I am too tired to fight
And run away from this filling light!
*Nightmares and shadows*
*Together we'll drown in the sea*
Believe me!
You'll walk by my side!