♪
[ INTRO PLAYS ]
♪ WHEN I WAS DONE DYING,
MY CONSCIENCE REGAINED ♪
♪ SO I BEGAN MY STRUGGLE,
A NOTHINGNESS STRAINED ♪
♪ OUT A FLASH MADE OF TIME,
MY NEW FORM BLASTED OUT ♪
♪ AND IT STARTLED ME SO,
AND I BURST OUT A SHOUT ♪
♪ AT WHICH MY LEGS RAN FRANTIC
LIKE BIRDS FROM A NEST ♪
♪ AND I RAN UNTIL DRAINED,
LEAVING NO CHOICE BUT REST ♪
♪ SO I FELL ASLEEP SOFTLY
AT THE EDGE OF A CAVE ♪
♪ BUT I SHOULD HAVE GONE DEEPER
BUT I'M NOT SO BRAVE ♪
♪ AND LIKE THAT I WAS TORN
OUT AND THROWN IN THE SKY ♪
♪ AND I SAID ALL MY PRAYERS
BECAUSE SURELY I'D DIE ♪
♪ AS I CRASHED DOWN AND SMASHED
INTO EARTH, INTO DIRT ♪
♪ HOW MY SKIN DID EXPLODE,
LEAVING ONLY MY SHIRT ♪
♪ BUT FROM SHIRT GREW A TREE,
AND THEN TREE GREW A FRUIT ♪
♪ AND I BECAME THE SEED,
AND THAT SEED WAS A BRUTE ♪
♪ AND I CLAWED
THROUGH THE GROUND ♪
♪ WITH MY ROOTS AND MY LEAVES ♪
♪ AND I TORE UP THE SHIRT,
AND I ATE UP THE SLEEVES ♪
♪ AND THEY LAUGHED OUT AT ME
AND SAID, "WHAT IS YOUR PLAN?" ♪
♪ BUT THEIR QUESTION
WAS FOREIGN ♪
♪ I COULD NOT UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ WHEN THEN SUDDENLY I'M RIPPED
UP AND PLACED IN A MOUTH ♪
♪ AND IT SWALLOWED ME DOWN,
AT WHICH TIME I HEAD SOUTH ♪
♪ SO I SAID, "HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY,
YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ WELL, I WOKE UP TO SEE THEM,
THESE TWO MIGHTY STEEDS ♪
♪ WITH THEIR MOUTHS
GRINNING WILDLY ♪
♪ EXPRESSING MY NEEDS ♪
♪ AS THEY STOOD THERE ABOVE ME,
BEING FLANKED ON EACH SIDE ♪
♪ I FELT NO NEED TO FEAR THEM,
NO REASON TO HIDE ♪
♪ SO I REACHED UP TO TOUCH,
BUT THEY FADED TOO SOON ♪
♪ YET THEIR MOUTHS
STILL REMAINED ♪
♪ AND STACKED UP
TOWARDS THE MOON ♪
♪ HOW THE LADDER OF MOUTHS
WAVES SO SOFT IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND I LOOKED UP IN AWE
AT THAT BEAUTIFUL SIGHT ♪
♪ AND I DREAMT ABOUT CLIMBING
INTO THE NIGHT SKY ♪
♪ BUT I KNEW,
HAD I TOUCHED THEM ♪
♪ THEY'D MOUTH BACK "BYE-BYE" ♪
♪ SO I GOT UP AND WALKED
DOWN THE PATH IN THE DARK ♪
♪ AND THERE,
DEEP IN THE DISTANCE ♪
♪ MY EYE CAUGHT A SPARK ♪
♪ OF A CRAB TWICE MY SIZE
WITH INCREDIBLE STRENGTH ♪
♪ OH, IT GREETED ME KINDLY,
AND THEN WE ALL DRANK ♪
♪ AND WE DROOLED OUT TOGETHER
RIGHT ONTO THE GROUND ♪
♪ AND THE OCEAN GREW QUICKLY
RIGHT UP ALL AROUND ♪
♪ AND THE EARTH LOOKED AT ME
AND SAID, "WASN'T THAT FUN?" ♪
♪ AND I REPLIED, "I'M SORRY
IF I HURT ANYONE" ♪
♪ AND WITHOUT EVEN THINKING,
CAST ME INTO SPACE ♪
♪ BUT BEFORE SHE DID THAT,
SHE WIPED OFF MY OWN FACE ♪
♪ SHE SAID, "BETTER LUCK NEXT
TIME, DON'T WORRY SO MUCH" ♪
♪ WITHOUT EARS, I COULDN'T HEAR,
I COULD JUST FEEL THE TOUCH ♪
♪ AS I FELL ASLEEP SOFTLY
AT THE EDGE OF A CAVE ♪
♪ BUT I SHOULD HAVE GONE DEEPER,
BUT I'M NOT SO BRAVE ♪
♪ I SAID "HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY,
YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ HEY, YA-E-YA, HEY, YA-E-YA,
HEY, YA-E-YA ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
[ WAVES LAPPING ]