I hope you don't mind
That I put down in words
How wonderful life is
now you're in the world
I sat on the roof and I kicked off the moss
Well some of these verses, well they
They've got me quite cross
But the sun's been kind while I wrote this song
It's for people like you that keep it turned on
So excuse me forgetting, but these things I do
You see I've forgotten if they're green or they're blue
Anyway, the thing is, what I really mean
Yours are the sweetest eyes, I've ever seen
And you can tell everbody this is your song
It may be quite simple but now that it's done
I hope you don't mind, I hope you don't mind
That I put down in words
How wonderful life is, now you're in the world