When I am down and, oh my soul, so weary
When troubles come
and my heart burdened be
Then, I am still
and wait here in the silence
Until you come and sit awhile with me
You raise me up,
so I can stand on mountains
You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas
I am strong, when I am on your shoulders
You raise me up... To more than I can be
(Ooo...)
You raise me up,
so I can stand on mountains
You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas
I am strong, when I am on your shoulders
You raise me up... To more than I can be
You raise me up,
so I can stand on mountains
(Stand on mountains)
You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas
(Stormy seas)
I am strong, when I am on your shoulders
(I am strong. Ooo)
You raise me up... To more than I can be
You raise me up,
(Raise me)
So I can stand on mountains
(Raise me, raise me up)
You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas
(You raise me up)
I am strong, when I am on your shoulders
You raise me up... To more than I can be
Bind me not to the pasture
Chain me not to the plow
Set me free to find my calling